Hello everyone!
Good evening!
Today's Monthly Magazine has started again!
Yes!
Good morning!
I've been up!
I've been on the last page...
Yes!
So what are we going to do today?
Or...
Positively a little different.
I'm not sure if you can tell from this.
Is this because my birthday's coming up?
Is it?
Is that what this is about? So you're not coming till winter?
I'm not coming till winter.
Since it's so close, we're going to have a celebration.
Today is the King of the Sketchy Champs 2023!
Yeah!
Yay!
We are celebrating!
Yes, we did it last time on the cover.
This time, it's the battle to determine the King of Skechan!
We're going to decide which cover you all got.
I'll find out today if you're watching.
Did you see the people channel?
It's that cap.
You've been watching the caps?
I see. I see.
I saw your mother's appearance.
Oh, wow, that's great.
Are you watching?
Is Kiyori really watching?
No, she's not really watching.
I'm looking.
I saw it. I just saw it.
Yeah, so, she said it's better that way.
Really?
No, I just saw you looking at it and I don't get it.
Yes!
Okay, let me explain the rules.
There are some rules.
There are 13 questions in total.
For each correct answer, you get one point.
One point for each correct answer.
We'll give you one point for every 13 questions you answer.
If you get the most answers for 13 questions
You will have the most points.
Who was it last time?
Oh, Yui or me?
No, it's not me.
Was it me?
No.
Oh, maybe it was you.
The winner of the one-day face-off is the same age as you.
You've been together for what, six days now? We've been together for what, six days now?
Started high school at the same time.
Graduated from high school at the same time.
Someone's going down.
We've been through the same thing.We've been through the same time.
Mr. Hiyori is at the bottom of the list.
Yesterday, he went out of his way to see my picture
who came to see my first love
Mr. Hiyori is in last place.
At any rate, the winner is...
The winner?
It wasn't even close.
And yet...
Alise's evolution...
Maybe it'll work this time.
The last place...
She was Carl's age.
That's for sure.
I miss him the most.
I'll never hit the bottom.
Well, I'd like to continue.
Let's get started!
Please comment and join in!
First question, this one is really easy!
I really think it's probably, what? Seriously, it's easy.
Is that okay? I'm not sure.
Here we go, first question.
What was the first song you tried your hand at singing?
This one is easy.
It's easy, but maybe not so easy.
Write it down with the official name.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay? It's hard.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Thank you for your help.
What?
Huh?
Oh, wait.
I know the title,
This one, quite a bit,
This is pretty...
It might be difficult.
Wait, wait. No, no, no.
It's because a lot of people are doing it.
That's for sure.
Wait, maybe this isn't it.
Finish it!
I made a mistake.
It's over.
Eh, this is different.
Wait, wait, wait.
Eh, I got the song title.
I know the name of the song.
But..,
I'm sure.
Oh, no. Wrong.
Ah,
Okay, then, one by one
Let's announce our answers one by one.
Okay, let's start with Kanamin. Go ahead, Min.
I'm getting a hit.
Oh, I see.
Sorry.I'm sorry.
What?
Why?
How do you say this?
I don't know. I don't know.
Me?
By the way,
I'll ask you later.
Okay, Asra, your ad.
Amazing!
Aki-chan!
Akira!
Great stability!
Lastly, Hiyori, please.
Akira!
So cute!
Aho!
Fool!
Ho-ho!
Dickhead!
Fool!
Aho!
Mr. Abo!
That's what this is.
I hope that means he's trying to be funny.
It's not! First of all, Ashley didn't come out at first.
But I knew it was your song, so...
It's an experimental version.
So let's just go with Ms. Abo.
Ms. Abo.
I wonder if any of them are correct.
Let's start the VTR.
What was the first song you sang or tried to sing?
What song did Hito-chan try to sing for the first time?
Ashira-chan.
I was the first among the members to try it,
It was also the first song I tried to sing.
No, I don't know if I could write it in Kanji characters.
Oh, I said "in kanji characters".
Now, here are the Kanji characters.
Here it is!
Oh!
Hachannelina!
Ooh!
One point for Oran!
By the way, Junior, what kind of song is this "I"?
That's a song about an idol.
Was it a cue to call this one?
Yes, that's why Kan-chan got 1 point in a row.
That's great.
This one is completely difficult.
Yes, it is completely difficult.
I sang a little bit, and the prediction is good, though.
Yes, it is.
We still have a few more easy assignments from here.
So, please, please.
I would like to go to the next assignment.I would like to go on to the next issue.
Yes, I will.
Let's go. This one, too, I know. Like this.
Ta-da!
What is ℃-ute's favorite hairstyle?
Yes, I do.
Let's start thinking time!
What?
What's that?
Not this?
Think about it, everyone.
Is this not it?
This is good.
If it wasn't this way, it would be hard for me to do it.
I think this is the one.
I'm confident about this one.
This is easy.
I see.
I think it's a service point.
Because this is not this.
This one, right?
This is it, isn't it?
What?
No, I was thinking of two, but one?
I love it!
Done!
Everyone's already playing.
Okay.
Okay, let's start with Calamine.
Follow me!
Twintails.
Oh! All together!
Let's see the correct answers!
Here we go!
What is Hito-chan's favorite hairstyle when she has a big bowl restaurant company?
Hito-chan's favorite hairstyle is
Hmmm...
Twin-tails!
Twin-tails are the cutest and I love them!
So Hito-chan's favorite hairstyle is twin-tails, so we are all cute!
Everyone got 1 point in a row!
Was this too easy?
This one was easy too!
Okay, let's continue.
Oh, this one is easy too!
Oh no, maybe they're all easy!
Let's go to the next question.
Let's see...
Which part do you like best in the song "Love Iyate"?
Part?
Oh, Tatamari.
What is your favorite part of the songs in Love Iyate?
Oh, what?
Others?
My own
My own?
What? What?
What, are you saying this?Oh, you're saying this?
I didn't say it because I didn't say the lyrics.
What about you, Hito-chan?
The lyrics.
I want you to meet me with this.
Hmm?
You didn't?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, so this is it then?
You're not going to sing?
But on my own count.
But I never said I liked it here.
What?
Aki-chan's favorite.
Okay, camera, please.
Think about it.
Think.
Flutter, flutter, flutter.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I made a mistake.
Too fast.
What? Why? I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. You two do it like this.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's right.
Because we're...
It's in the AI.
I just checked with the A.I.
Oh, yeah.
It's recorded.
Pull yourself together, please.
This could be it.
Is it?
It could be this one.
Okay, let's hear the correct answer, please.
He's laughing.
This is, actually, a fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering.
Ice-ee!!!
Now it's my favorite.
At first it was difficult and I was kind of like, what am I going to do?
Now that I can sing it, I like it because it gives me a sense of accomplishment.
That's great.
Yes, so the correct answer was at the fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering fluttering.
So, I was born again and got 14 pints,
Oh, my gosh!
That's amazing.
It was in Skiede that I learned to sing,
Before I learned to sing, it was really difficult,
I was so worried that I might get it,
But I overcame it recently. Now that I can sing it, I like it.
It's great.
I also like Nipete.
I like Aki-chan all the time.
Yes, I like it when I say I like it.
I like all of them, but I like this one the most,
Amazing.
Seriously.
It's amazing.
Only adults can do that.Only adults can do it.
We encourage everyone to try the Hirahira Challenge.
Hirahira Challenge
Now, let's continue.
Now, the dance is 3.
3?
From the specialists.
All of them?
So far. That's what I'm talking about.
Hey, guys, we got a service issue.
Yay!
Maybe we can all get points.
Here we go.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Kacchan's.
Yay!
This is good,
This is fine.
Last time, Kanabin did it too, right?
There was a brand spelling.
So, I think everyone has done their homework.
That's right. I'll get this one already.
Maybe I was a little too nice.
I knew this question would come up.
I'm prepping for it.
I understand.
When you start a brand, everyone spells out the brand.
So with that, let's start with Kanabin, please.
Leo.
Let's see then. Let's take a look.
Go ahead.
Tomo-chan, please write the cell for the producer's round.
Did everyone get it? This is not so simple.
Yes, it is. Here is the correct answer.
DADADADADAN... Eh?
Oh, that's right.
LEO.
It was L-E-O-H.
Did you get it?
Yes, I did. So, the correct answer was
LEO.
Everyone got it right.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
You will all receive one car point.
Yay.
Two points.
Wait a minute.
Except the end.
Hey.
I'm sure.
Am I being too easy? The question.
So much for what we heard.
Is that what this is about?
That's what it's about? Really?
Next.
This one's easy, too.
I'd like to move on.
Here is the next question.
How old is Nikkahana's dog, Reia?
This one.
I think this one is easy.Here, I think it's easy.
It is.
New Nurturing Department.
Yes, it was cute today with the two choices.
I think it was this one.
I think it's this one.
Wait a minute.
I have two choices, but the two choices are double the number of times I've done this.
I'm sure.
I think it's this one.
I don't know.
But it might have been like this.
I think it was like this.
This is it. Maybe.
What?
They're here?
Yeah, they're here.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, let's start with Kanamin.
Eight years old, one step.
Eight. Eight. Eight.
Four. Four.
What? Wait.
Four is gone.
No more 4 years old. 4 years old.
Four years old.
Okay, then,
Please.
You saw his face.
The way she looks at Hiyori.
You know, the way she looks at you, the way she loves you.
Yes, my favorite Leo, you know how old he is, don't you?
My Leo was 8 years old.
People always think he's a baby.
But he is actually 8 years old.
He's so cute!
So the correct answer is...
He was 8 years old.
Aki-chan on camera...
You won one in a row and lost!
Yay!
Um...
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
Because I...
When the group was formed...
About two years later.
Around the year we formed.
That's about right.
You remember that?
What? Did you lose your memory?
No, I don't know.
I was nine this year.
What month?
December.
Oh, December!
Yes, I will be 29 years old.
I may be playing Shi-chan, so please try to remember that.
Yes, and now?Yes, so now what?
Good morning, more like 5.
5!
Kanamin-san, Kanamin-ji and Aki-chan are 3, and Hiyori is 4.
Ah!
Yes!
Hiyori is leading for now.
Aren't they all correct?
Right!
That's great!
Let's continue.
Now continue!
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak!
Let's go for it!
Ah! This one might be easy too!
Oh! Really?
Let's go!
There you go!
The latest version! What's your favorite fish, KITO?
Let the thinking theme begin!
Oh, no!
Did you say that?
Yes, I did.
What?
What? You said it!
You were talking like Sabakitai.
We never talked about Sabakitai.
That was me.
What? Where's your fish, Kito?
It's the newest version!
What? What? What's the newest version?
Grilled fish.
Not sashimi.
That's a little syncretic.
Okay, okay!
What's the newest version? What's the newest version? Is there such a thing as new-fangled fish?
I think I'm telling you.
In the story.
With the guys.
That's a fish, right?
Oh, my God!
You're kidding!
That's it.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
End
Absolutely finished.
Now, please start from the kana-bin in order.
Thai Cuisine
Salmon
Tutu
Aiyu
Now, is there a correct answer in this list?So, are any of these correct?
I'll watch it on the VTR!
That's a great range, Kanabin!
Wait for the delivered version of Hito-chan's favorite cleanup!
Yes, my latest favorite fish is
Nodoguro (northern bluefin tuna)!
It's so delicious!
I like it so much I want to eat it every day!
I've never had it before!
So, the correct answer was nodoguro!
I've never had it!
Once I had it, I was hooked!
I was so addicted to it
I haven't been able to get out of it.
But I love fish that is hard to eat.
I love it!
So, the correct answer was
Imasayo.
I've never eaten it!
but I love them all!
Thank you very much.
The next question is...
Next, the next question is...
What? Who knows?
Those of you who were there may remember it.
For those who weren't there, it might be a little difficult, but here goes.
What is the length of Hito-chan's pants? The length from your waist to the floor.
Let's start Thinking Time!
You know, I'd like you to do some kind of measuring time.
You were measuring at that time.
This is also bad. I'm going to be out of time.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
Here you go.
Sure thing.
I'm confident about this.
Heh.
Is he here?
No, he's not here.
Oh, no?
No, I'm all alone.
I'm not sure.
Okay, then.
I'll go alone.
69.5 cm
92cm
105 cm
I have no idea what I'm talking about.
Okay, PTR please.
How many is from your waist to the floor?
Yes, this is the size that the manager always measures me when he takes my measurements,
I wonder if anyone who was there could figure this out.
Only the pants from the waist down.
100cm was 1m.
Yay!
I got it first.
I'm so disappointed.
Yay!Yay!
It's so tiny, isn't it?
Yes, so the correct answer is,
100cm, 1m,
Karami's correct answer!
Yay!
It's Karami's first win in a row.
That's great.
Wow.
I remembered something today.
What? Who was with you at this time?
Pullian was with me.
We were together. Because they were in the 5:1, 5:1.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
When we measured in Osaka,
Yes, yes.
It was actually 1 meter.
That's great.
That's a relief.
Please remember that.
Thank you.
Seino. Sex Pineapple
Ao said?
He said 3 times, 3 times, 5 times.
But it was delicious.
It looks delicious.
It was delicious.
Next time preview
Next time, I'll show you what I'm talking about.
Ta-da!
In Hito-chan's first solo camping video,
What did Hito-chan eat in her first solo camping video?
Well, it's my first time.
Your first campfire video?
The first one was my self-introduction,
After the introduction, she makes her first bonfire,
Um, please write down everything.
Everything?
This one, that one is fine.
Uh, hiragana is fine. All.
All?
All. How many?
Please write down the ones that come to mind.
No, I'm just...
I don't know if you can tell. I guess.
What? Watch this. What is that?
You can't have the ingredients, can you?
There's no ingredients.
Ingredients?
I don't think so.
How many ingredients?
Ingredients.
I meant ingredients.
Ingredients?
Yes, sir.
Okay, bye.
From Carabin.From Carabin.
Please.
Meat? Ramen?
Marshmallow ramen meat
Marshmallow ramen
Marshmallow to go in a pot
Meat, marshmallow, and risotto.
Yes.
So, since there are correct answers in here,
Okay. Now, please go to the VTR.
This one might be a little difficult,
The first one was marshmallow, the second one was meat, and the third one was northern ramen.
Did everyone understand?
You got 1 point for 3 correct answers.
Yes, I did. So, that's it,
Yes. So, the correct answers were,
Marshmallows, meat, steak, and Nifang Ramen.
So, Julia, you didn't have nikata,
Correct!
You eat a lot.
Yes, I did. I ate those three.
Oh, that was close.
I could have guessed it from the marshmallow.
So, Julia won the first place.
Let's continue.
Maybe you can guess this one too.
Let's go.
What is Hito-chan's favorite outfit for the time selection?
Start Thinking Time!
Well...recently?
No, I don't know. Maybe this one?
Maybe this one.
Do you like it?
What? What is it?
I have no idea.
It's totally cute.
Yes, they're all cute.
Oh, I get it.
What?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know, you know, if you write down the features or something.
Wow, I'll change it.
I'll change it.
What?
Time's up for number one.
Then, please start with the perfume.
It's not good.
Miss Worker.
Ah, the sanctioned costume.
Embrace.
Insta-costume.
Yes.
It's quite different.
Let's start with the VTR, please.
Q.What is your favorite costume today?
A. My favorite costume is the Girls' Land costume from 2022.
I really like this one because it has a twin-tail neck and it makes my legs look longer.
It's different!
It's a keyboard.It is a keyboard.
You have to have a drawing.
I've got the one I drew before one,
It's different.
How did you do it?
Chidoribara-sensei's,
The one with the red pen.
I always like that one.
It's the most stylized one I've ever seen.
She wore her hair in twin-tails.
Twintails.
It doesn't happen often, but twin-tail hair.
That's why I like it.
That's cute.
Yes, that's why,
I have four more questions to go,
I'd like to look back at the results so far,
I'd like to take a look back.
Oh, really?
Calami has 4 points,
4 points for Karami, 4 points for Julia,
Oharu has 5 points,
Aki-chan has 3 points,
Aki-chan has 3 points, and Hiyori has 2 points.
That's a really good competition.
It's a good competition.
They're totally copying me.
I still have 4 points,
You have a chance to get back in the game from here,
Please do your best.
I'll do my best.
Now, let's move on,
I'll let you all guess this one on a hunch.
Hito-chan was at the dance yesterday, right?
Okey.
I guessed on a hunch.
By intuition.
Just a hunch.
But it's just a hunch.
By intuition.
But it's a hunch.
A hunch.
It's a hunch.
Let's go.
It's okay.
I'll let you imagine me, and then Calamine will start, please.
2:30.
25:00.
2:00.
1:30.
Ugh!
What?
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes!Yes!
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
What?
So, I've been sleeping well.
I'd like to offer you a prize.
Yes, Hito-chan, what time did you go to bed last night?
What time did you think?
The correct answer is
2 o'clock.
Oh, no.
At 2 o'clock,
I fell asleep before I realized it.
Amazing.
Today is amazing.
What?
What? What's going on?
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Five minutes.
Not five minutes.
Not yet. Balloon.
So, the correct answer was,
It was 2:00.
Oharu has won 1 Rion coin.
That's amazing.
After all, we've been living next to each other for 8 years.
That's great.
I was getting a little scared.
She saw me.
Don't worry. I didn't do anything strange.
It's big here.
I didn't do anything strange.
But at 2:00,
I just wanted to check the time one last time.
Oh, so you went to bed?
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
It's already 2:00.
It's 2 o'clock.
Yes, it is. So, Oharu is the point now.
Amazing.
Hair ring?
One point.
I'll do my best.
Okay, let's see what we can do,
Three questions left.
What about this one? Can you figure it out?
Here we go.
What is the average time Hito-chan spends doing her own makeup?
I'm seriously looking forward to it. Start!
I feel like I was doing something.
I remembered and was talking about myself.
This is about the same today.
Just face?
Makeup?
Maybe.Maybe.
I don't know.
I didn't say time to take care of my skin
Sunscreen.
That's about all I do.
That's about right.
You're not that dark.
That's me today.
I don't know.
Did you guys put it on?
Yeah, I did.
Okay, let's start with Carvin.
Ten minutes.
30 minutes.
20 minutes.
15 minutes.
Ten minutes.
That fast?
Can we get in here?
What?
Okay, VCR, please.
Yes, sir.
Q. Ms. Kawamura, do you spend an average of time doing your own makeup?
Yes, the average makeup time is
Sometimes I do a lot of makeup, and sometimes I don't.
When I do a lot, it takes 2 to 30 minutes.
and 5 to 10 minutes when I don't.
15 minutes.
15 minutes of makeup time.
The correct answer was 15 minutes!
So, that's 10 points for Aki-chan!
That's fast!
I've often heard people say they did their makeup in 10 minutes.
Sometimes I make it 10 minutes.
When I don't have to be on camera, but can be a bit popular, I usually do it in 10 minutes.
Honestly, I just put on eye shadow, eyebrows, blush, and sunscreen,
I don't know... 15 minutes?
That's amazing! Aki-chan.
I wish I had a puree.
I changed it.
Maybe you shouldn't have changed it.
So, only 2 questions left!
Now,
Now, Karami has 4 points, Julia has 4 points,
Oharu has 6 points, Aki-chan has 4 points,
Hiyoyumi has 2 points.
Good luck, Hiyomi!
Will it be the same as last year and last time?
Hiyoyumi.
Why?
Hiyoyumi, go for it!
Hiyoyumi-chan, go for it!
Okay, let's go,
This is easy!
Skip problem!
Here we go!
I didn't write the problem because it's really, really easy.
If you were to travel abroad, which country would you most like to visit?If Hito-chan were to travel abroad, which country would you most like to visit?
Start!
Where?
Where would you go?
What?
Overseas.
I'm sure you've thought it through.
I don't know about that.
I don't know.
Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
What?
I don't know.
I want to see it.
I don't want to see it.
I want to see it! I want to see it! I want to see it!
Which one?
How do you know?
I wonder... I wonder...
Is this not it?
I don't know.
I've never seen it before.
I wonder where it is.
I've seen it. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
But, oh!
Ten seconds left.
Only one?
One!
Just one!
I don't know.
Three.
Two.
One.
So, that's it.
Time is up, so...
From Salamine.
please.
Hawaii
Nope.
Korea
Hawaii
Singapore
Yes!
Now, can you find the correct answer in this list?
Please!
I see it!
Go ahead!
Hito-chan, since you are going abroad, which country do you want to go to the most?
Yes, the country Hito-chan wants to go to the most is Hawaii!
I have unforgettable memories of going to Hawaii,
I would like to go back to Hawaii and go to places where I can eat and play in the ocean, go on a variety of boats, etc,
I want to go back to Hawaii and play in the ocean and ride on a variety of boats.
I haven't come back at all.
I'm going back.
Yes, so the correct answer was Hawaii!
So, I have a series of points for the colorful Doha!
I want to go!
I've been to Hawaii, Hawaii, and I enjoyed it so much that I want to go back as many times as I can.Hawaii, Hawaii has been there, and I've enjoyed it so much I want to go back as often as I can.
Because I feel like I'm saying it so much.
I love Hawaii!
The best thing is Hawaii!
I want to go to Hawaii!
I want to go!
I want to go! Please do!
So, is this the last one?
The last one.
Oops.
But, you know, everyone thinks about this.
Are you okay?
What? Leo, are you on board?
Don't worry about it.
What are we gonna do?
Make a turnaround?
Ah!
Right now, Kanamin has 5 points.
Okay, so 3!
If I add 3, 2?
If it's 2, I'm winning.
Kanamin and I are tied.
If Kanami gets 2...
Well, let's just say
Let's just go with 1 point.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's go with one point for me, too.
No, you're wrong.
But I'm reversing.
Two!
Hiyori...
You're the one who's invited to come in last!
Two.
Well, I'll go with two.
The last one is the special point
I'll do my best
Oh, that.
Really.
Good luck.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
Let's make it 45 seconds.
What?
I knew it. One minute.
Okay, then.
Last problem.
Draw a portrait of Hito-chan.
Draw a cute portrait of Hito-chan.
The person who gets the most points will win.
For this purpose, we'll give you points as well as a score.
Make it cute.
For this purpose
Pretty
For this problem we're going to come up with
Pretty? Well, let's see what I like best and how I draw it.
It's important to say that it's cute and similar.
Twenty seconds left.
I've done portraits before in demonstrations,
Everyone will come out with a picture in various shapes.
5 seconds left: 4, 3, 2, 1, end!
Everybody's done.Everyone is finished.
Calamine.
Everyone is safe.
It's funny that there's no calamine.
Good day to you,
Are you okay? Calamine.
Are you okay?
Okay, let's start with Calamine.
Shall we go?
Calamine, go ahead.
Jelia, you want to go?
I want to go.
Let's go.
Hmm?
Ha-ha-ha.
What's this?
Just a little...
Doggy!
Doggy face.
I think it's pretty good.
Not bad.
What? Our doggy is pretty cute.
Next.
Here you go.
Leah!
Ah!
Looks like a go-go!
Oh, Rhea.
No, uh, a little bit...
Rare-ish
A little bit of doggie-ness.
There's one over here, too.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Tiny, tiny, tiny.
What?
Just like a baby.
It's full of...
It's nice.
Eh, they'll change it.
Cute.
Eh, they change it.
Eh, it's cute.
You're so cute.
It's my life.
I can see it.
Your mouth is so cute.
It's a heart.
Even her eyes are hearts.
Your mouth is cute.
Cute.
Cute mouth.
My favorite.
Cute mouth
Cute mouth.
Yes, it is.
And...
And the eyes are hearts.
Your mouth is cute.
And hearts all around.
And the...
HeartHeart
Amazingly cute.
Your mouth.
I kinda regret making this problem myself.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ehhhh...
It's pretty cute.
Here's another one.
Well then.
Now, let me make an announcement.
The most adorable drawing is
DODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODODO!
Julian!
Oh, those eyes!
Oh, those eyes...
Dodododododododododododododododododododododododododododododododododod
Okay, as a point of review,
Something like, um, first of all,
I don't have pure eyebrows,
I quite like eyebrows, don't you?
Yes, they are distinctive.
And, you know,
When you're idolizing,
I think it's important to have sparkling eyes,
I thought it was important to have sparkling hearts,
So I decided on this one because of the heart-shaped eyes,
So I chose this one!
Yay!
So, Julia got 2 points,
The final results are in!
But the bottom and top are different.
Karalyn got 5 points, Julia got 6 points, Ohayu got 7 points, Aki-chan got 4 points, and
Ohayu got 7 points, Aki-chan got 4 points, and Hiyori got 2 points,
Akichan with 4 points, and Hiyori with 2 points,
Hiokao is hatchers!
Amazing!
That's great!
Continuing from last time, Ohayu is the hatcher!
I knew it!
I was surprised. I didn't think I would get such a good score.
Because, you know,
Almost all of them were 7 questions, right?
More than half of them were correct.
That's amazing.
But what about Hiyori?
Look at how it's written.
The words "Punish Love" are written.
Continuing from last time,
We're the same age, and we've been going out a lot lately.
You couldn't possibly know that.
I know you do,
You do.
She says it's the same as last time.
That's funny.
It's pretty frustrating.
Frustrating?
It's frustrating.
But, I guess what's done is done,But a sarekae is a sarekae,
Hiyori's punishment game was,
She was punished by being as cheeky as Hito-chan and saying a line to Hito-chan at a close distance.
To Hito-chan?
To me?
A chair, then.
Well, I'll do it first.
And I won't lose.
How about I do it first, and then you do it as good as I do it?
Without the blur.
No blur.
If you go for the blur, that's the first thing I'll do,
No.
That's a disqualification.
Let's go for maximum mockery.
Oh.
Sucks a lot
Okay, here we go...
I like you.
Okay, can I wave to you for a second?
Like this.
Huh?
Use this a lot.
Okay, Pion will do it.
Okay, let's see,
Three, two, one.
Like this,
And extend.
Like this.
What's this?
Hmm.
...
I'm in.
Oh, wow.
Okay, say you like it.
Tell me you like me.
I like you.
Do you like it?
I don't want it.
Tell me you like me.
Uh...
This is what happens to people.
If someone does this to me, I'll do this.
Okay, so...
That's all... I'm a natural.
Bye bye!
That was the most embarrassing thing I've ever done
I don't know why, but when I smile, the world seems to glow
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure there's someone crying somewhere, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted, guiding me along
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the streets are turning colors
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
When it's raining, I'll try to smileSo that when it rains, we can still smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Thank you for watching.